<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Movie Facts</string>
    <string name="movie_name">Toy Story</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="toy_story_fact">In November 1993, reels of Toy Story were brought in front of
        Disney executives who decided to halt production and nearly gave up on the project.
        Three months later, Pixar came back with a reworked script and the film was saved.</string>
    <string-array name="movie_fact_array">
        <item>In November 1993, reels of Toy Story were brought in front of Disney executives who
            decided to halt production and nearly gave up on the project.Three months later, Pixar
            came back with a reworked script and the film was saved.</item>
        <item>A Bug\'s Life is based off Aesop\'s fable The Ant and the Grasshopper.</item>
        <item>Toy Story 2 was originally going to be a direct-to-video release. After Disney saw
            the reels, it was changed to a full length theatrical film. It is now considered one
            of the best animated films of all-time.</item>
        <item>Billy Crystal, the voice of Mike Wazowski in Monster\'s Inc., was originally offered
            the role of Buzz Lightyear in Toy Story but declined.</item>
        <item>Finding Nemo director Andrew Stanton is the voice of Crush the sea turtle. Originally
            doing the voice as a stand in, Stanton thought they would eventually find an actor but
            his voice proved popular in test screenings and stayed in the film.</item>
        <item>The Incredibles story was influenced by director Brad Bird\'s own struggles
            balancing his career goals and family life.</item>
        <item>Cars was inspired by Director John Lasseter\'s own road trip across the country with
            his family.</item>
        <item>Pet rats were kept in the hallway of Pixar for over a year during production of
            Ratatouille so the artists could more accurately depict rat movements and behaviors
            in the film.</item>
        <item>The robots in WALL-E all follow science fiction author Isaav Asimov\'s Three Laws
            of Robotics.</item>
        <item>It was estimated that 23 million balloons would be needed to make Carl\'s house fly
            in Up. To avoid the balloons looking too small, the number of balloons depicted range
            from around 10,000 to 20,000.</item>
        <item>The final scene of Toy Story 3 is of white clouds against a blue sky, the same
            backdrop as the opening scene of original Toy Story that shows the wallpaper of
            Andy\'s room.</item>
        <item>The idea for Cars 2 came from director John Lasseter\'s experience travelling around
            the world promoting the original Cars movie and wondering what Mater would do in the
            different countries.</item>
        <item>The hard to understand dialect of Young MacGuffin in Brave is actually a Doric
            dialect spoken in northeastern Scotland.</item>
        <item>The campus of Monsters University was inspired by the campuses of UC Berkeley,
            Stanford, Harvard and MIT.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="movie_name_array">
        <item>Toy Story</item>
        <item>A Bug\'s Life</item>
        <item>Toy Story 2</item>
        <item>Monsters, Inc.</item>
        <item>Finding Nemo</item>
        <item>The Incredibles</item>
        <item>Cars</item>
        <item>Ratatouille</item>
        <item>WALL-E</item>
        <item>Up</item>
        <item>Toy Story 3</item>
        <item>Cars 2</item>
        <item>Brave</item>
        <item>Monsters University</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
